This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy launched a desperate attack on Navy Headquarters
in hopes of saving his brother from execution.
However, his struggle ended in vain,
with his enemies claiming an overwhelming victory,
along with Ace's life.
But Brother Ace is really dead, isn't he?
Yes, I'm afraid that he is.
Luffy and Ace, the story of how the brothers met.
No one could have guessed it at the time,
but the path that led Luffy to Marineford began long ago.
Ten years ago, in fact, in the East Blue.
There lies a small town known as Windmill Village,
where people lived quiet, peaceful lives.
But it was the nearby Mount Corvo,
where few would dare to set foot.
For only the strong could survive in its dark woods,
faced with beasts that would make quick work of trespassers.
What's wrong with being king of the pirates, Grandpa?
The pirates are... cool!
And what makes you think I care?
I'm gonna... slap you!
Eating that devil fruit wasn't enough trouble for you?
Now this nonsense?
You and your big brother, Ace,
are going to become fine Marines.
You understand me?
Ow, ow, ow, you suck!
I thought I was supposed to be made out of rubber now.
Why does this still hurt so much?
I thought leaving you in a nice village would keep you safe,
but pirates won't be satisfied
until they get their grubby hands on everything.
And I forbid you to associate with that red-haired Shanks.
He's a terrible influence.
Ah, it's awesome!
Now I'm gonna be just like it!
Oh, yeah!
What's this dump?
Hey, shut the hell up!
Whatever it is you're selling, I don't want knives!
Put it on!
Huh?
Ah!
Garp, what are you doing here?
Hmmm...
Charming as ever.
Sorry for the cold welcome,
but I hope you don't have another ridiculous favor to ask us.
You realize Ace is already ten, right?
Oh, is he now?
And how's the little scam doing? Good?
Well, there's a handful, of course.
And we've been watching over the brat for long enough.
So just take him away.
Never mind.
Yeah, that's the problem. We do mind.
Speaking of breath, would you shut that one up?
He's yours now.
Hey, Luffy, tell him hello.
Yo!
Wait a sec. Who is he?
He's my grandson.
Huh?
What?
I never heard about this.
And you want us to take care of the little monster.
A little darling, I mean.
Well, no way.
Fine. Then I'll give you two choices.
You can either raise my grandson or spend your life in prison.
Pretty generous, considering all the crimes you've committed.
No fair.
The thing is, I'd rather stay out of the slammer.
Frankly, if you ask me that on one of Ace's bad days,
I might have to go for the prison option after all.
And two brats?
Yeah, I don't think so.
This kid looks like a real charmer, too.
Like your face?
You want to fight, you little punk?
He, he, he, he, he.
Oh!
The door!
Don't let him get to you!
Huh?
Ew!
Spit!
That's gross!
Who did that?
Hey!
You jerk!
You better apologize for that!
Huh?
Hey!
There he is!
Oh, hello, Ace!
Welcome back!
I'm waiting!
Luffy, this here is Ace.
He's three years older than you.
Anyway, you're going to be living with him and Dadan from now on.
What?
Not so fast!
You play nice.
We said no!
You'll do it.
Sir, as you wish, sir!
Well, time to hit the road.
I'll stop by again when I have time.
What about some child support?
Put it on my tab.
This isn't a bar.
Huh?
Nothing!
Come back soon!
Boss, we're bandits.
We can't take in another kid.
Shut up and fix dinner.
We'll figure it out.
Thanks, ma'am.
Say you're sorry!
Hey, come back!
I'll leave this hat to you.
Where did he go?
Hold it!
Let me go!
Give me all your money or I'll kill you!
I don't got any.
I'm a kid!
Fine!
Then go tell your parents to bring us their money!
I have a grandpa!
Okay, good enough.
Tell us his name and we'll go find him.
It's Garp.
Not the Garp!
And the kid's going to be staying with us from now on.
How did you agree to this?
We're not running a daycare here!
Screw a spine!
That's enough!
It's dinner time, boys!
You can argue when you die!
I want the big one!
Screw you!
Lights on first!
See some for me!
Hey!
You already ate your affair, pal!
Give me!
I'm not losing to you, youngster!
You share or you die!
Survival of the fittest, my friends.
Broke his arm!
Come on!
It's your turn to do this.
Oh, man.
Can I have some more?
I'm a woman, thank you very much!
Do you even know where you are right now, you filthy little urchin?
No.
Okay, then I'll tell you.
This is the den of the Dodon family.
Mountain bandits that rule Mount Corvo.
Mountain bandits?
Mountain bandits are lame.
Well, you're stuck with us.
Or rather, we're stuck with you, thanks to that pushy grandfather of yours.
But if you don't want to stay, that's fine by me.
Go get eaten by a bunch of wolves for all I care.
Easy, boss. Easy.
I just wanted some more rice.
For me, it would be nice.
In case you didn't notice, all this meat came from that bison ace brought back.
Even though he's a kid like you, he has to work to earn his cape.
The bandits' life's a hardwood boy.
Tomorrow, you're going to pay in blood, sweat, and tears.
Cleaning.
Doing laundry.
Policing our boots and weapons.
Robbery, fraud, murder, and terror.
And if you go crying to your dear old grandpa, we'll string you up without a second thought.
One bowl of rice and one glass of water, that's all I can promise you.
The rest you get for yourself.
You're going to have to grow up real fast, kid.
Or you're going to go hungry before the week's up.
No problem.
No problem?
Not crying and begging for mercy?
Grandpa threw me in the jungle one time, so I know how to tough it out just fine.
There's plenty of water to drink, and I can eat frogs and snakes and mushrooms and stuff all I want.
I'm going to be a pirate someday, so we've got to be strong.
This is going to be real fun.
Boss!
You okay?
Hurry, help her up!
Keep home!
Why is he leaving?
One more!
Hey, get back here, you!
Hold on!
What do you mean you're going to be a pirate?
And stop ignoring me!
Hey!
He just got here, and he's already a pain.
It's going to be like having a baby garp living with us.
No, no, it's okay.
Hey!
Wait for me!
Hi!
My name's Luffy!
Everything's cool now!
I'm not mad about you spitting on me!
Why are you all laughing?
But the guy just spilled some booze on me.
It's not worth getting bent out of shape.
It's not worth getting bent out of shape!
I'd rather be friends!
So can I come with you?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Ace is back.
You know what that means.
Boom!
Huh?
Wait, you're alone?
That's not good.
Oh, yeah.
Where's Luffy?
Wasn't he with you?
Beats me.
Come on, you snot-nosed brat.
Where did you go?
You think maybe he died out there?
If he did, it's going to be our funeral, too.
The boss must be worried sick right about now.
Ugh.
Get a hold of yourself.
This is serious.
No biggie.
Oh, and is that what you're going to say to Garb when he finds out we let his grandson die?
Why do you care?
One less crappy brat in the world.
I have a feeling that Garb won't see it that way.
Well, maybe the old jackass should have thought about that before he left him with a bunch
of bandits in the woods.
Come on, does this look like a damn daycare to you?
If he can't take care of the boy himself, he has no right to talk.
You should tell him that, not us.
Suck it!
If Gold Roger had a son, what are you talking about?
He'd end up just like his dad.
Off with his damn head.
Then he'd probably cry and shut him down for good.
I'm trash just like my dad.
I should die.
You know what?
While we're at it, screw Ace too.
If he dies, we'll tell Garb it was an accident.
I mean, that'd be the truth, wouldn't it?
The devil's children have the devil's luck.
How about that?
Because Ace is the devil's son for sure.
What do you think the government would do if they found out about him?
I'll take my chances with Garb.
Nay, you don't mean that, boss.
Come on, that's the booze talking.
Just sleep it off.
One week later.
Damn dog.
Don't you know we're trying to sleep?
Boss, wake up.
Come here, quick.
It's you.
The little bugger isn't dead after all.
You're alive.
Why'd you scare us like that?
Huh?
Easy, easy, boss.
Where the hell were you and what were you doing?
Now, now, just give him a second.
He'll answer without all the face stretching.
I was stuck in the bottom of the valley, getting chased by wolves.
Are you nuts?
What the heck were you trying to do down there?
Well, whatever.
It's good you came back safe.
There's nothing good about it.
Another useless mouth to feed.
Get some sleep while you can.
We're putting you to work bright and early tomorrow.
Oh.
Hey, Ace.
You going somewhere fun today?
Take me.
I know I was gone for a while, but I still want to be friends.
Wait.
Boss, he's running after Ace again.
Hey.
Get back here.
You still have chores to do.
I'm out of here.
I am going to wring your rotten neck, you twerp.
Easy, easy.
You shut your yapper and go bring him back.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey.
Liz.
He's dead.
Hey.
Come on! I want to be friends with you!
The next day.
Hey, Ace! Let's be friends!
Do your damn choice, kid!
He's already gone.
Well, hurry up and bring him back then!
You're not getting away from me today!
That's easy!
So are we friends yet?
And on the tenth day...
Luffy!
You're too late again. He's already long gone.
Then bring him back!
It was the same thing every time.
But that didn't deter him one bit.
A month passed.
Two months.
Wait up!
In the rain...
Or in the wind.
Whoa!
Let's be friends!
Ace would run and Luffy would chase him.
Again? What does that moron think he's gonna accomplish?
He's getting banged up pretty bad out there.
He's bound to lose interest sooner or later.
Let's hope!
This nonsense is really stressing me out!
You're worried about him, aren't you?
Don't be stupid!
I'm just mad because he's not pulling his weight!
The leehive fell on my head.
Luffy!
Come back!
I'm not giving up yet!
I'm having a tough time losing him today, stubborn punk.
Hmm?
Uh-oh.
Crap.
This sucks!
Got away again!
How'd he get so darn fast?
Hey!
There you are!
That's gotta be the nastiest monster in the forest.
Even I can't beat that thing.
Run away, stupid.
It's gonna eat you.
I want to run away, but my legs won't let me!
Damn it.
Step up.
neighивает.
Ahh!
No, no.
Ahh.
Ahh!
Ahhh!
Hmmm.
Jungle bit!
Akui!
Ah!
Ahhh!
Ahh!
Ah!
hurry!
Oh
Three months had passed, and although he was covered with cuts and bruises, Luffy did not
relish.
It's the end of the forest.
What is this place?
Mountains of discarded trash reach toward the sky in the criminal-infested junkyard known as Gray Terminal.
With dreams of buying a pirate ship in their hearts, Ace and his partner in crime, Sabo, robbed the thieves and scavengers in this den of lawlessness.
On the next One Piece, here comes Sabo, the boy at the Gray Terminal. I'm gonna be king of the pirates!